AoM Photographs 5289 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AoM Photographs
1969-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Academy of Management (AoM)
5289 P
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Photographs.
8047626
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 06, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 19, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The Academy of Management is a professional organization that thrives on member-driven efforts to further the scholarship of management across many categories. With a rich history in volunteerism, many projects have resulted from our members' collaboration and passion for their work.[http://aom.org/about/]
Scope and Contents
This collection is photographs of members attending Annual Meetings.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5289: AoM Records 5289 MB: AoM Memorabilia 5289 PUBS: AoM Publications 5593: AoM Records 5772m: Keith Davis Papers 5893m: Leonard R. Burgess "Status of Women in Academy of Management" Memoir 5904m: Paul Gordon Collection of Academy of Management Miscellany 5920 AV: AoM Audio-Visual Collection 5977 mf: AoM Additional copy of publications on Microfilm 6019: AoM Eastern Academy of Management Records 6117: AoM Additional Records 6134: AoM Publications Additional Publications 6278: David Van Fleet Collection of Academy of Management Records
Academy of Management
8047626
- Photos from Annmarie Koory (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  36 photographs
- Academy of Management (Box 1, Folder 2)
  33 photographs
- Contact Sheets (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Academy of Management 1969 Meeting (Box 1, Folder 4)
  1 photograph
- Richard Strassberg at Ives Hall, Cornell University 1982 (Negative #800203 - Roll 1, Frame 17) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  10 photographs
- 1989 Annual Meeting (1) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  26 photographs
- 1989 Annual Meeting (2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  17 photographs
- Fellows Annual Meeting 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  3 photographs
- Fellow Annual Meeting 1993 (1) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Fellows Annual Meeting 1993 (2) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Fellows Annual Meeting 1993 (3) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  25 photographs
- Photos from 1995 meeting (1) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Photos from 1995 meeting (2) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Photos from 1995 meeting (3) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Photos from 1995 meeting (4) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Photos from 1995 meeting (5) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Photos from 1995 Meeting (6) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  28 photographs
- Fellow Dinner - Anaheim, 1988 (1) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Fellows Dinner - Anaheim, 1988 (2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  12 photographs
- Fellows Annual Meeting - Fullerton, CA, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  32 photographs
- Fellows Annual Meeting - Washington, DC, 1989 (1) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Fellows Annual Meeting - Washington, DC, 1989 (2) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Fellows Annual Meeting - Washington, DC, 1989 (3) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fellows Annual Meeting - San Francisco, 1990 (1) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fellows Annual Meeting - San Francisco, 1990 (2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Fellows Annual Meeting - San Francisco, 1990 (3) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1993 Annual Mtg. of Academy of Management (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 1993 Annual Mtg. of Academy of Management (1) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 1993 Annual Mtg. of Academy of Management (2) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 1993 Annual Mtg. of Academy of Management (3) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  9 photographs